// // topics = ["Fruit Plants", "Flower Plants", "General"]

// quizzes = [
//   {
//       topic: "60ed20efb22379018056acd2",
//       question: "Where was the kiwi fruit first grown?",
//       correct_answer: "China",
//       incorrect_answers: ["New Zealand","Australia","Chile"],
//       explanation: ""
//   },
//   {
//       topic: "60ed20efb22379018056acd2",
//       question: "Which fruit has the highest oil content?",
//       correct_answer: "Olive",
//       incorrect_answers: ["Avacado","Peach","Mango"],
//       explanation: ""
//   },
//   {
//       topic: "60ed20efb22379018056acd2", //fruit topic
//       question: "Papain is a natural digestive aid that is found naturally in:",
//       correct_answer: " Papaya",
//       incorrect_answers: ["Mango","Banana","Lychee"],
//       explanation: ""
//   },
//   {
//       topic: "60ed20efb22379018056acd3", //flower topic
//       question: "Papain is a natural digestive aid that is found naturally in:",
//       correct_answer: " Papaya",
//       incorrect_answers: ["Mango","Banana","Lychee"],
//       explanation: ""
//   },
//   {
//       topic: "60ed20efb22379018056acd4", //general topic
//       question: "Papain is a natural digestive aid that is found naturally in:",
//       correct_answer: " Papaya",
//       incorrect_answers: ["Mango","Banana","Lychee"],
//       explanation: ""
//   },
// ]

// module.exports = {topics}

quizzes = [
 
  {
      topic: "60ed20efb22379018056acd2",
      question: "Which fruit has the highest oil content?",
      correct_answer: "Olive",
      incorrect_answers: ["Avacado","Peach","Mango"],
      explanation: ""
  },
  {
      topic: "60ed20efb22379018056acd2", //fruit topic
      question: "Papain is a natural digestive aid that is found naturally in:",
      correct_answer: " Papaya",
      incorrect_answers: ["Mango","Banana","Lychee"],
      explanation: ""
  },
  {
      topic: "60ed20efb22379018056acd3", //flower topic
      question: "How is Cerastium tomentosum colloquially known?",
      correct_answer: " Papaya",
      incorrect_answers: ["Candytuft","White allysum","Snow-in-summer"],
      explanation: ""
  },
 {
      topic: "60ed20efb22379018056acd3", //flower topic
      question: "The Hanging gardens of Babylon are in which modern day country?",
      correct_answer: " Iraq",
      incorrect_answers: ["Lebanon","Jordan","Iran"],
      explanation: ""
  },
{
      topic: "60ed20efb22379018056acd3", //flower topic
      question: "In which US state are the most tomatoes produced?",
      correct_answer: " California",
      incorrect_answers: ["Florida","Ohio","Indiana"],
      explanation: ""
  },
  {
      topic: "60ed20efb22379018056acd4", //general topic
      question: "Which of these sweet smelling plants is highly toxic to humans?:",
      correct_answer: " Lily of the valley",
      incorrect_answers: ["Rose","Freesia","Lilac"],
      explanation: ""
  },
 {
      topic: "60ed20efb22379018056acd4", //general topic
      question: "What is the State flower of Florida?",
      correct_answer: "Orange Blossom (citrus sinensis)",
      incorrect_answers: ["Peach Blossom (prunus persica)","American dogwood (cornus florida)","Sunflower (helianthus annuus)"],
      explanation: ""
  },
{
      topic: "60ed20efb22379018056acd4", //general topic
      question: "What planting conditions do hellebores favour?",
      correct_answer: "Well-drained, partial shade",
      incorrect_answers: ["Full sun","Boggy, partial sun","Open, windswept"],
      explanation: ""
  },
]

module.exports = {quizzes}
